# NGWA FRANK NEBA FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

+237 673220094



frankneba92@gmail.com



Bamenda Cameroon



Ngwa Frank

#### SUMMARY

I am a frontend web Developer with over a year of experience and a mastery of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript And React.js. I have some knowledge in C, C++ and python with knowledge on version control systems like Git and Github. I have worked on many projects with different individuals in building user friendly and easily navigated websites. While learning and improving on my skills I have been providing others with the knowledge I have especially knowledge on C to students going in for Cameroon GCE advance level. I am looking forward to working and collaborating with others in completing projects and expanding my skill set

## **EDUCATION**

2023 - present

National Higher Polytechnic Institute Bamenda Bachelor in Computer Engineering

2020 - 2023

**Progressive Compressive High School Bamenda** Science

2013 - 2016

**Government High School Bafut** 

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML
- Good communication skills.
- CSS
- Fluent in English language.
- Javascript Respects dateline for tasks given.
- React.is
- · Comfortable working remotely.
- C
- · Effective in problem solving
- C++
- Python

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Frontend web developer

Zilotech, 2024- Present

- Comprehensive administrative assistance to Management.
- · Building friendly user interfaces.
- · Review of documents suitability and file control.
- Collaborates with team members in producing quality products
- Implemted responsive designs and improved user interfaces of websites

#### Frontend Developer Intern

Zilotech, 2023 - 2024

- · Built websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript with frameworks like Bootstrap and react js
- Applied responsive design to produce beautiful views for both mobile and computers
- Provided ideas for data base designs and implementation for backend
- · Collaborated with a team of developers in completing projects

## CERTIFICATES

- Bachelor in Computer Engineering (pursuing)
- GCE Advance Level General 2023
- Best Student Northwest Region GCE Advance Level General Cameroon 2023

#### LINKS

GitHub: gitHub.com/frankneba

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/ngwa-frank-a88747298